[
  {"question"  :"A XOR B",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... (A OR B) not (A AND B) ",
   "id"        : 0  
  },
  {"question"  : "A NOR B",
   "answer"    : ["uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... not (A OR B)",
   "id"        : 1
  },
  {"question"  :"A XNOR B",
   "answer"    : ["inter","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... not (A XOR B)",
   "id"        : 2  
  },
  {"question"  :"A → B",
   "answer"    : ["c2","uni","inter"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... not A OR B ",
   "id"        : 3  
  },
  {"question"  : "B → A",
   "answer"    :["c1","uni","inter"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... not B OR A ",
   "id"        : 4 
  },
  {"question"  : "A NAND B",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2","uni"],
   "hint"	   : "It is equivalent to... not (A AND B) ",
   "id"        : 5
  },
  {"question"  :"A ∧ B",
   "answer"    : ["inter"],
   "hint"	   : "∧ = AND ",
   "id"        : 6
  },
  {"question"  : "A ∨ B",
   "answer"    : ["c1","c2","inter"],
   "hint"	   : "V = OR",
   "id"        : 7
  },
  {"question"  : "¬(A ∨ B)",
   "answer"    : ["uni"],
   "hint"	   : "¬ = not",
   "id"        : 8
  },
  {"question"  : "Well Done!! Go to the next level...",
   "answer"    : [""],
   "hint"	   : "",
   "id"        : 9
  }
]
